{
    "subject": "Judy_Dickinson",
    "predicate": "isMarriedTo",
    "object": "Gardner_Dickinson",
    "human_readable": "Judy Dickinson is married to Gardner Dickinson.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9718154668807983,
            "question": "Who is married to Gardner Dickinson?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.97010338306427,
            "question": "To whom is Judy Dickinson married?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.966701328754425,
            "question": "Is Judy Dickinson married?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9422721266746521,
            "question": "Is there a relationship between Judy Dickinson and Gardner Dickinson?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9344925880432129,
            "question": "Name the spouse of Gardner Dickinson."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8245354890823364,
            "question": "What is the name of Gardner Dickinson's spouse?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7717501521110535,
            "question": "What is the marital status of Judy Dickinson?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6828888654708862,
            "question": "Who are Judy Dickinson and Gardner Dickinson related to each other?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6513028144836426,
            "question": "Who shares a marital bond with Gardner Dickinson?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5449874997138977,
            "question": "What is the name of Gardner Dickinson's partner?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Judy Dickinson is married to Gardner Dickinson.",
            "html": "yago_19161_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who shares a marital bond with Gardner Dickinson?",
            "html": "yago_19161_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who are Judy Dickinson and Gardner Dickinson related to each other?",
            "html": "yago_19161_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the marital status of Judy Dickinson?",
            "html": "yago_19161_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_19161_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_19161_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_19161_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_19161_21.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_19161_25.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_19161_38.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_19161_43.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_19161_5.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_19161_50.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_19161_63.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents mention that Judy Dickinson was married to Gardner Dickinson, which supports the statement."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "mistral-nemo": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "-",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}